<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>php on Reece&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>/tags/php/</link>
    <description>Recent content in php on Reece&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>My Name</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/php/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PHP Stock Photography Ecommerce site</title>
      <link>/2022/03/12/project-phpecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/03/12/project-phpecommerce/</guid>
      <description>Created a php stock photography site with paypal integration
Description: A Web site with the ability for client to add, rearrange and sell photos. As well as displaying thumbnails on the site to prevent theft.
Tooling: Vim, PHP, HTML, CSS, Javascript, MYSQL, ImageMagick, Bootstrap, PayPal, Trello, Figma, PlantUML, Markdown, Shell
Methodology: Agile
Design Pattern: Procedural PHP with templating
Version control and Deployment: Git, XAMPP, phpMyAdmin
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP and XAMPP on linux</title>
      <link>/1/01/01/phponlinux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/1/01/01/phponlinux/</guid>
      <description>References php builtin server undefined function undefined mysqli function php how to conect to dbs using pdo and mysql php detailed mysql and pdo crud
Steps  install it with bitnami from their site it goes into opt lampp set up the ports configuration uncomment the mysqli extensions include the extension directory extension_dir = &amp;ldquo;/usr/lib/php/modules/&amp;rdquo; setup how to do the connection use /opt/lampp/bin/php to test properly change track_errors to off from on never use php always /opt/lampp/bin/php  FOR ME  figure out way to get phpserver to serve the mysqli modules mysqli_connect works but need to now use my way of accessing it use how i access it with mysqlroot i have to use 127.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
